http://www.superiorboiler.com/privacy/

News
We’re Hiring!
Sales
United States
Global Sales
English
Arabic Chinese (Simplified) Dutch English French German Italian Portuguese Russian Spanish
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy explains how we collect, use and protect your personally identifiable information (PII) through superiorboiler.com. In terms of information security and US privacy law, PII is information that can be used to identify, locate or contact an individual person.
Types of Information Collected
You may be asked to enter your name, address, email address, phone number or other details to allow us to fulfill your order or process your request.
When Information Is Collected
We collect information from you when you submit a contact form, subscribe to our email list, browse the website or enter other information on our site.
How We Use the Information
We may use the information you provide us with to allow our sales representatives to process your order and/or to send you periodic emails about your order status or other service and product updates.
How We Protect Your Information
Your personal information is only accessible by a limited number of people who have administrative access needed to process your order. These team members are required to keep our customers’ information confidential. In order to make the best product recommendations and make future orders easier, we store your data securely unless and until you request for it to be deleted.
All sensitive information you provide to us is safely encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL). Your transaction information is not stored or processed on our servers. All transactions are processed through a secure gateway provider.
Use of “Cookies”
This website uses Cookies, which are small files that transfer from a website to your computer’s hard drive if you allow them to do so. Cookies allow the website or the service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and remember some information.
We use cookies to help us to understand your preferences and improve our services for you. We also use cookies to help compile general data about our website traffic and usage to help us improve the site experience and tools in the future. We may use trusted third-party services to track this information on our behalf.
You may choose to turn off all cookies, which is done through your browser settings. Doing so will disable some features that make a more efficient site experience, but you will still be able to use the website.
Third-Party Disclosure
We will not sell, trade or transfer your personally identifiable information to outside parties without providing advance notice. Information may be made available to our partners and other parties who assist us with managing our website, operating our business and serving our website users. These partners agree to keep the information confidential. Information may also be released to comply with the law, to enforce website policies or to protect someone’s rights, property or safety.
Non-personally identifiable website visitor information (aggregate data) may be provided to other parties for the purposes of advertising, marketing or other uses.
Google Analytics
We use Google Analytics on our website, which compiles aggregate data on website usage, demographics and interests.
Opting Out
Users may opt out of Google advertising or change their preferences for how Google advertises to them by visiting the Google Marketing Opt-Out Page or by going to the Network Advertising Initiative Opt-Out Page.
California Online Privacy Protection Act
CalOPPA is a state law requiring commercial websites and online services to include a privacy policy on their site. In compliance with CalOPPA, we agree that:
Users may visit our site anonymously
This privacy policy will be linked to either our home page or the first significant page after entering our website
The link to our privacy policy contains the word “privacy” and can easily be found on our site as indicated above.
You will be notified via email of any changes to our privacy policy. You may change your personal information by emailing us or by logging into your account.
Do Not Track Signals
We honor Do Not Track (DNT) signals, and do not plant cookies, track or use advertising when a DNT browser mechanism is in place.
Third-Party Behavioral Tracking
We allow third-party behavioral tracking for the purposes stated above.
COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)
We do not market specifically to children under the age of 13 years old.
Fair Information Practices
In accordance with Fair Information Practice Principles, we will notify you within 7 business days should a data breach occur.
We also agree to the individual Redress Principle, which states that individuals have the right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data processors and collectors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle also requires that individuals have recourse through courts or government agencies who may investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance of data processors.
CAN-SPAM Act
We collect your email address for the purposes of responding to inquiries, requests and questions; to process orders and send updates about their status; to send you additional information related to our products and services. This may include marketing to subscribers on our email list or sending emails to our customers after the original transaction has occurred.
In accordance with CAN-SPAM, we agree we will not use any false or misleading subject lines or email addresses in our communications. We will reasonably identify that the message is an advertisement, and we will include the physical address of our business. We will also monitor third-party email marketing services, if used, for compliance with CAN-SPAM. We will provide a link in each email that users may follow to unsubscribe, and we will honor opt-out and unsubscribe requests quickly.
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you may follow the link at the bottom of each email and we will promptly remove you from receiving any future messages.
Other Websites
Our website contains links to other websites. This privacy policy applies only to superiorboiler.com, so if you click on a link to another website, you will need to check that website’s privacy policy to see how they handle your information.
Contacting Us
If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us as follows:
Superior Boiler
Data Protection Officer: Nick LeJeune
nlejeune@superiorboiler.com
Last edited 5-11-2020
Contact Sales
Select RegionSelect RegionUnited StatesAfricaAsiaCanadaCaribbeanCentral AmericaSouth AmericaSelect StateSelect StateAlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareDistrict of ColumbiaFloridaGeorgiaHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinWyomingArmed Forces AmericasArmed Forces EuropeArmed Forces PacificFirst Name*Last Name*Email*
Phone*Message*NameThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
BUILT to OUTPERFORM
Superior Boiler Works, Inc.
3524 E. 4th Avenue
Hutchinson, KS 67501
(620) 662-6693
SITEMAP  |  PRIVACY
Website Design & Development by Balefire Marketing + Advertising
